p-e-p.com 2019-08-13

# Planet Earth Projects Privacy Statement

Planet Earth Projects respects your preferences concerning the collection and use of your personal information and is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy notice applies to information collected by this web site, except where stated.  Planet Earth Projects provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used.  Planet Earth Projects may change this policy periodically by updating this page. Please revisit to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

By accessing this website, you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws.  If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site.  The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.

#### **What information we collect and how we use it:**

If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Statement.  Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purpose for which information is being collected.

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information, including phone number(s), mailing and email address
  * Demographic information such as postal code, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and compatible purposes, unless we obtain consent of the individual concerned as required by law.

We will retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying use or modification.

We will not sell or give your contact information or any related information to a third party.

Personal data will be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete and up-to-date.

#### **Cookies**

We use cookies to identify which pages are being used.  This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to our customer needs. These cookies do not reveal information about you that you have elected not to reveal. Your web browser settings may be adjusted to limit or prohibit this and other web sites from placing cookies.

#### **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us in writing or in email.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law or to fulfill specific requests if necessary. We may use, or have a partner use, your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act.  A small fee will be payable.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible.  We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
